## Jenny Menase jennymenase@protonmail.com (202) 494-6398

I am looking to start a career in computer technology. I spent several years in accounting, management, and process improvement. I took software classes to increase my technical depth and am looking to move into an analyst or technical position where my attention to detail and creativity can help a company and colleagues maximize their potential.

## **Core Technical Skills**

	Proficient	Exposure
Languages	Java, Powershell, Bash	JavaScript, Python
Frameworks	Spring, Spring Boot	AngularJS 1.x, Node.js, jQuery
Markup/Tag -Languages, Data Formats	HTML5, CSS3	JSON, XML, Maven, Gradle
Databases	SQL	MongoDB
OS Platforms	Windows, Linux, OS X	
Protocols	НТТР	
Strengths	Analytical, Focused, Flexible, Communicative	
Other Tools	Git, Amazon Web Services, Google Analytics, J-Unit Testing and TDD	

## **Professional Experience**

US Anesthesia Partners Greenwood Village, Colorado December 2012-September 2016

Lead Payment Posting Specialist

I started at this company doing data entry and worked my way up into payment posting and a leadership role. I interviewed, mentored, and trained new employees throughout two mergers.

- Created workflow manuals
- Worked with management to integrate two dozen employees over the course of four years
- Used Microsoft Excel to create detailed analytic reports for monthly finances

The Ellison Medical Foundation Bethesda, MD

March 2010 – November 2012

**Grants Administrator** 

I helped to process grants applications from researchers who wished to receive funding for aging research.

- Designed organizational systems for 400+ applicants yearly
- Maintained files for over 600 total awardees
- Tracked institutional assurances and reports for current awardees
- Created a database of all projects from 1999 through 2012

## Education

University of Maryland, College Park: B.A., Spanish Languages, Literatures, and Cultures (May 2009) Skill Distillery Java Coding Bootcamp, Denver, CO (October 2016-February 2017)